# KEIICHI KATSUNO

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER /
RELATIONSHIP MANAGEMENT SPECIALIST



## PERSONAL SKILLS

- Emotional Awareness
- Team Management / Teamwork
- Project Management
- · Problem-Solving
- Business Relationship

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails (Ruby)
- Javascript (ES6)
- HTML5 / CSS / Bootstrap
- SQLite & PostgreSQL
- GitHub / git

# LANGUAGES

- Japanese (Native)
- English (Professional)
- Spanish (Elementary)

#### INTERESTS

- Weight Training
- American Football
- Non-Fiction (e.g. Anthropology / History / Business etc)
- Specialty Coffee

## CONTACT

20 Newton Street Kensington, Victoria 3031 045 255 3653 keichi031605@gmail.com

- Linkedin: keiichi katsuno

- GitHub: keiichi031605

#### **PROFILE**

A Coffee & Tech Enthusiast. Deep interest in SaaS and passionate about creating a solution for business improvement. Enjoying working & living in a new environment with new technology.

Experienced Relationship Management and Production Management over the world for the past 6+ years. This journey has given me much confidence and ability to collaborate with diverse people. I'm competent in Team Management and Teamwork and proud of my emotional awareness for building firm relationships as well as solving the problems and meeting the needs.

# **PROJECT**

#### "WHATSPOT" (SOCIAL NETWORKING SERVICE)

- The mobile app that you can share any places or recommendations with your friends so that you get more reliable information.

URL: https://www.whatsthespot.com | Built in Ruby on rails.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **QUALITY ASSURANCE SPECIALIST**

InverCafé Ltda., Chinchiná, Colombia | Sep 2019 - Dec 2019 (Internship)

Green Coffee Quality Assurance

- Developed: "Smooth Communication" / "Individual Collaboration"

#### PRODUCTION MANAGER

The Roasting Shed Co., London, The UK | July 2018 - Sep 2019 (Full-time)

Specialty Coffee Production Management

- Developed: "Task Management" / "Efficient Teamwork"

#### **RELATIONSHIP MANAGER**

Yuasa Trading Co., Japan | Apr 2013 - July 2017 (Full-time)

Business Partnership Management and Account & Order Management - Developed: "Market Research" / "Business Relationship" / "Problem-Solving" / "Project Management" / "Individual Collaboration", while doubling my area sales targets within a 12-month period!

## **EDUCATION**

#### **FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT, COMPUTER SCIENCE**

Le Wagon Melbourne | Apr 2020 - June 2020

## **BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION, SPORTS MANAGEMENT**

Kinki University, Osaka, Japan | Apr 2009 - Mar 2013

- **Activity:** American Football Club, learning Organisational Theory, Team Management and Teamwork